Porn, the internet and the girl next door.
Hot Girls Wanted is a documentary film directed by Ronna Gradus.
A first-ever look at the realities of the professional “amateur” porn world and
the steady stream of 18-to-19-year old girls entering into it.
Self, played by Stella May.
Self - Founder of Hussie Models, played by Brian Omally.
Self, played by Ava Taylor.
Self, played by John Anthony.
Self - Tressa's Mother, played by Kelly Silguero.
Self - Tressa's Father, played by Emeterio Silguero.
Hot Girls Wanted is a 2015 American documentary film
directed by Jill Bauer and Ronna Gradus.
The film follows the lives of several 18- and
19-year-old pornographic actresses.
The film premiered at the 2015 Sundance Film Festival and
was released on Netflix on May 29, 2015.
The film explores themes of porn star, softcore,
craigslist, woman director, adult filmmaking.